tv-online-channels.com 2015-03-30

# tvlive32.com Privacy Policy and Terms of Use

**General Terms of use**

If you make use of this site you agree to respect the rights of the content owners. If not you should leave this site. tvlive32.com does not provide or host any audio or video streaming content. This site is designed to enable users of personal computers and other consumer electronic devices to easily find and access media content over the Internet. Unless otherwise stated, we or our licensors own the intellectual property rights in the website and material on the website. Subject to the licence below, all these intellectual property rights are reserved. All TV channels are copyrighted by their respective owners. We claim no ownership, connection, affiliation, with any of the TV channels played on this site. We do not provide streaming content ourselves. tvlive32.com only includes free TV channels streamed by the owners themselves, without to include tv channels streamed by non-owners. The TV streams found on this site are found freely available around the web. We are not responsible for the content of the TV stations. The owners of the TV channels are responsible for their content. 

**Tv Station Removal**

If you think the tv station you represent is listed by mistake on tvlive32.com please notice us at contact[at]tvlive32.com and the tv station will be removed in 24 hours. 

**Limitations of liability**

The information on this website is provided free of charge, and you acknowledge that it would be unreasonable to hold us liable in respect of this website and the information on this website. Our liability is limited and excluded to the maximum extent permitted under applicable law. We will not be liable for any direct or indirect loss or damage arising under these terms and conditions or in connection with our website, whether arising in tort, contract, or otherwise. Without limiting the generality of the foregoing exclusion, we will not be liable for any loss of profit, contracts, business, goodwill, data, income, revenue or anticipated savings arising under terms and conditions or in connection with our website, whether direct or indirect, and whether arising in tort, contract, or otherwise.

**Indemnity**

You agree to defend, indemnify and hold harmless tvlive32.com, from and against any and all claims, damages, obligations, losses, liabilities, costs or debt, and expenses (including but not limited to attorney's fees) arising from: (i) your use of and access to the tvlive32.com website; (ii) your violation of any term of these Terms and Conditions; (iii) your violation of any third party right, including without limitation any copyright, property, or privacy right; or (iv) any claim that one of your User Submissions caused damage to a third party. This defense and indemnification obligation will survive these Terms and Conditions and your use of the tvlive32.com website.

**Privacy Policy for tvlive32.com**

Please feel free to email us at contact[at]tvlive32.com for any question or information regarding our privacy policy.

**What information do we collect?**  
We do not ask users to register or to provide any personally identifiable information to use our site. We may collect and use the following kinds of non-personal informations: information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website, such as your IP address, geographical location, browser type, operating system, referral source, length of visit, number of visitors and number of page views.We never collect personally identifiable information about users such as names, adress, e-mail addresses or telephone numbers. We may use such non-personal information for internal purposes, including but not limited to improving the content of our sites. tvlive32.com does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13.

 **What do we use your information for?**  
Any of the information we collect from you may be used to improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

 **Do we use cookies?**  
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

 **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

 **Third party links**  
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include links directly to sites operated by third parties. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. All links to external sites are opened in a new window. tvlive32.com is not responsible for the content or practices of Web sites operated by third parties that are linked to our site.

 **Online Privacy Policy Only**  
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

 **Your Consent**  
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

 **Changes to our Privacy Policy**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

This policy was last modified on 02.07.2011

http://tvlive32.com
